<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://usatko.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://usatko.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2022-08-25T13:53:09+00:00</updated><id>https://usatko.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Tadej Justin, PhD, is currently chief data scientist at Medius d.o.o., a custom software development company, where they adopted Databricks platform to handle all their data, analytics and AI use cases. Tadej has more than 10 years’ experience in the field of machine learning. During his research studies, he focused on speech technologies and natural language processing. Nowadays he is actively promoting machine learning and data science as applied technology in every enterprise information system. With Medius, they have successfully applied machine learning in large companies and governmental information systems. # Tadej started his studies with the electrical engineering program at the University of Ljubljana in 2002. He enrolled into a Master study program covering fields of Automation and Intelligent systems. During his studies he was interested mainly in developing automated artificial system with the help of data mining related tasks. After completing an MSc in 2009, he enrolled into a PhD program at the same University. His main interest remained the same, strongly related with the field of pattern recognition. He focused in speech related technologies, such as emotional recognition from speech, emotional and cross-lingual parametric speech synthesis. You can check his work and publications on one of the well known research profiles as ResearchGate, Academia or Google Scholar. During his studies and research, he spent an amount of time developing Python related web-based platforms, as well administrate all Termitnjak&apos;s server infrastructure. He successfully defended his PHD thesis in 2016. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog</title><link href="https://usatko.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog"/><published>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</updated><id>https://usatko.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://usatko.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry></feed>